(Leonard:)I'm just saying, sometimes Raj
and I feel pushed aside.
(Raj:)Yeah. Like when you
took Sheldon to Texas
(Raj:)and showed him all around NASA--
(Raj:)you didn't even think
to ask me and Leonard.
(Howard:)You know what?
You're right.
(Howard:)I should have asked you.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, and if he does
ask you, go.
(Sheldon:)It's amazing.
(Howard:)Okay, and if
we're talking
(Howard:)about being left
out of things,
(Howard:)you guys went to Skywalker
Ranch without us.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I recommend that, too.
(Sheldon:)That was a magical
experience!
LEONARD:
Wait a minute.
(Leonard:)Sheldon spent a whole day
with James Earl Jones
(Leonard:)and never told any of us.
(Sheldon:)I sure did.
Oh, my goodness!
(Sheldon:)Well, from Jabba's head
to ice cream with Darth Vader,
(Sheldon:)I'm having a heck of a ride.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, look,
(Sheldon:)clearly, good
things happen
(Sheldon:)when I'm in charge.
(Sheldon:)Now, why don't
(Sheldon:)you boys step aside,
let me knock this project out?
(Howard:)Sheldon,
(Leonard:)you're not in charge.
(Leonard:)Raj is in charge.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, who's
really in charge?
(Sheldon:)The person in charge, or
those who put him in charge?